

# **MD. HOSSAIN ABIE**

# 3D Modeler, UI/UX Designer & Web Developer

As a dedicated 3D Modeler, Graphic Designer & Web Developer, I possess a unique blend of technical expertise and creative problem-solving skills. With a strong foundation in architectural and engineering design, I have honed my abilities in producing precise and detailed drawings using AutoCAD, ensuring that every project meets the highest standards of accuracy and functionality. My experience includes collaborating with architects and engineers to translate concepts into comprehensive plans, which has sharpened my attention to detail and understanding of design principles.



Full Name: MD.Shabbir Hosssain Abie



Date of Birth: 08/03/1993



Address: 153/5 Mohishbathan, Rajshahi Court, Rajshahi,BD



+8801307793777



>https://iabieport.onrender.com/



hossainsabie@gmail.com

### **Employment**

2016-Present

- Founder of "Kint3d" & Bluewave Dimension.
- Founder of "SABATO" T-shirt Printing Company.
- Founder & Senior Front-end Web Developer At "Frontendr" Web Development Ltd.
- Senior UI-UX Designer At Anyza AI.
- Graphic Designer at Teach Graph.
- Assistant Manager at EM Center.
- I have completed "Professional Project-based Training on Autodesk 3ds Max" in 2017.
- I have completed "Autodesk Autocad (2D & 3D)" Under The Bureau of Manpower Employment and Training (BMET) program in 2020, offered by Technical Training Center(TTC), Rajshahi.

2013-2014

Zaber & Zubair Fabrics Ltd. Pagar, Tongi,

Gazipur-1710.

**Graphics Designer** 

I worked here as a Graphics Designer (Print)

From 1st August 2013 T0 2014.

2011-2012

The Dacca Dyeing & Mfg Co. Ltd.

Pagar, Tongi, Gazipur-1710.

Jr.Executive

I worked here as a Jr. Executive (Admin)

From 1<sup>st</sup> August 2010 T0 2011.



#### **Personal Information**

**Father's Name** Late Md. Abdur Rais Mst. Samsun Nahar Mother's Name

Road: Mohisbathan, P.O-Rajshahi Court, Permanent

P.S-Rajpara, Building #: 153/5.

**Address** 

Gender Male **Nationality** Bangladeshi **Marital Status Unmarried** Religion Islam

**Blood Group** AB+

# **Education**

2016 **International Business Administration** and Information System

> Program: BBA. Major: HRM. Credits: 135. **Board: Dhaka. Passing Year: 2016. Result:** C.G.P.A- 3.40. Internship: Islami Bank Bangladesh Limited.

2011 Rajshahi Court College

Group: Science. Board: Rajshahi. Passing

Year: 2011. Result: G.P.A-4.10

2008 **Shahid Mamun Mahmud High** 

School & College.

Group: Science. Board: Rajshahi. Passing

Year: 2008. Result: G.P.A-4.19

## **Professional Skills**

3D Modeling **Graphic Design Photoshop** Illustrator MS Office **Video Editing** ...... VFX HTML



# Portfolio & Achievement

- https://iabieport.onrender.com/
- https://www.turbosquid.com/Search/Artists/kint3d
- https://www.turbosquid.com/Search/Artists/Blue-Wave-Dimension
- https://my-store-d826a8.creator-spring.com/
- https://www.fiverr.com/abie07

I am undersigned, hereby declare that the above information is true and correct to the best of my Knowledge.

Whatsapp: +8801307793777 | Hobby-Movie, Travelling, Songs, Long Drive | www.linkedin.com/in/abie-hossain | Facebook.com/mohammadabie